[narrator] Until that moment...
when the earth bore a creature.
They only need a man so strong.
So powerful.
So daring.
Unstoppable.
Unshakeable.
- [thwacks]
- [grunts]
They need...
Monsour Del Rosario.
Whatever demon you are
I'm ready for you!
[narrator] Tornado Jack!
Facing dangers in the mouth of Hell
in the name of all that is good.
- [gunshot]
- [grunts]
- [zaps]
- [explosion]
[grunts]
[echoes] Tornado Jack!
[crew 1] Sir Monsour is late.
[crew 2] Yeah, I think
he's going to take longer.
[crew 1] This might take a while.
- Let's eat first.
- Sorry, sir.
We're losing the sun.
Call him again.
[film rolling]
[rolling continues]
[thunder rumbles]
[water pattering]
- [car approaches]
- [engine stops]
[Camille] Good morning.
Good morning.
[Monsour grunts]
- [Monsour] Good morning.
- Good morning, Sir Monsour.
Good morning, Camille.
Uh... I saw the camera over there.
Move it to the other side. Okay?
- Okay, sir.
- Okay?
- Is Lav there?
- Yes, he is.
[explosion]
[heroic music]
- Good morning, Lav!
- [Lav] Hey!
Is it still "morning"?
- [Monsour] Hey, let's talk.
- [Lav] Mm-hm.
Uh, I want to change
the camera position
from the right to the left.
Because in all my films
my angle is always from the left,
never the right.
Secondly
I read the script.
I just left a scene
without saying a word.
I thought it would be good
if we put in some dialogues.
Let me know which one is better.
This is version one.
"Salazar...
you'll pay for this!
I'm taking this fight
all the way to hell!"
Ha? Now, this is version two.
[exhales]
"Salazar! We can do this in hell!
You'll pay for this!"
[Monsour] What are we going with?
Version one or version two?
- The first one.
- Yeah!
That's what I thought!
I also really liked the first one.
Okay.
Caloy, I need to internalize now.
There they are!
See this, buddy?
This will do it.
Two, three.
And then right, here.
Me and my muscles will look
really angry in this movie!
I'll be over here. Okay.
Let's take it here, guys.
Where's that girl from Shine?
Here, sir.
I need to speak to Andrea.
Where is she?
She's at the office, I'll call her.
Yes!
[grunts]
[tense music]
[Rina in English] Hey.
[in Filipino] Whatever happened
to waking up early
and going home for fresh clothes?
Sleeping in is way better.
[chuckles]
Why don't you go straight to work?
[in English] Why do you
have to go home?
[in Filipino] The staff will see me
wearing yesterday's clothes.
[Joey] Am I going with you
to your office?
Nope. Mommy's waiting for you.
Uh...
It's almost time to leave for Canada.
You have to start helping her pack.
Oh? Is this all you're taking?
- Can I zip this up?
- Wait! My robots!
[tense music]
[tense music continues]
- Next time...
- [Rina] Mm?
...pack a bag and leave it here.
So you won't have to rush going home.
That's a lot!
Of course!
There's food at the office.
Do I have to bring all of these?
You hardly eat, so yes, take it all.
Oh! Are you coming with me?
Yes, Andrea. I'm meeting some friends
near your office before I go back
- to the apartment.
- Okay.
Those two?
- Of course!
- Okay, put it here.
Here. This guy first.
You have a lot of toys.
Make sure to pick up after yourself.
Your mom's going to be busy
with her work, okay?
You should really come with us.
[Joey] You can pick up
my toys for me.
Tell Mommy to get you a ticket.
I think it's time to go. Come on!
- Just lock the doors when you leave.
- Yes. Go.
- [Karylle] Bye!
- You're going to be late.
- [Andrea] Thank you!
- [Rina] Take care!
[electricity crackles]
[smoke detector beeping]
[theme music]
♪ Careful, careful ♪
♪ The world is full
Of jealous people ♪
♪ When envy strikes,
It means trouble ♪
♪ That's why we need to be careful ♪
♪ Careful, careful ♪
♪ We always need to be careful ♪
♪ Prying eyes ready to snoop ♪
♪ Digging for the juiciest scoop ♪
♪ That's why we need to be careful ♪
♪ Careful, careful ♪
[suspenseful music]
SEN. FRANK TO ABS-CBN:
YOUR DAYS ARE NUMBERED!
Does ABS-CBN deserve to be shut down?
Frank Villacin is very influential.
Frank Villacin is all bark.
- Mm-hm.
- [telephone ringing]
[imitates Sofie]
Shine Artist Management.
This is Sofie. How may I help you?
[imitates Sofie]
Hello, yes. Sorry about that.
[Noemi] Sure, I'll transfer you,
please hold.
- [Chin] Your impression was spot on!
- Where's Sofie?
And why is it so hot in here?
- It's the AC.
- It's not working.
Her audition is today.
Did you leave the set?
- [Chin] You left?
- I said I had a meeting.
And I need a change of clothes.
Looks like we're going
into overtime again.
A lot of problems on this set!
Hey, the meeting's about to start.
I didn't know Sir Monsour was a diva.
[Camille] I was on the set
before he was.
- Can I leave this here?
- Sure.
[Noemi] What do you expect?
It's been so long
since his last film.
- [Chin] That's right.
- [telephone rings]
- You guys go ahead.
- Okay.
[Chin] Sir Samuel told stories
about him.
Hello?
[scoffs] Really?
Wrong number.
[playful music]
Why do you think
he's making a comeback?
Do you think he needs money?
No, he doesn't.
He's producing this film, right?
No wonder he acts like
he's king of the set.
I heard he's always been like that.
[Chin] It's so hot!
[Noemi] Deo, what is this?
What's going on?
[Chin] It's really hot!
Matthew, weren't you wearing that
the other day?
[Matthew] What?
What you have on.
[Andrea] You were wearing that
- the other day.
- [Matthew] I like it.
Okay, so for the next two years,
Rob is fully booked.
And the tax people have agreed
that the ads he'll do for them
will cover for his unpaid taxes.
Problem solved.
His projects will proceed as planned.
[in English] Okay. Great job!
Um...
Is there anything else?
Yes!
[in Filipino] Shouldn't we tell them?
Let's tell them the good news!
What good news?
[Andrea] About SAM!
[Matthew] Andrea.
I don't think we should.
We're not sure yet.
This is our core group.
They have to know, and...
Okay, anyway.
Guys, Matthew, Gabriel, and I
will be buying SAM
from Mrs. Helen Mendiola!
Oh, my god! Thank you, Lord!
I thought I was losing this job!
So you're each paying one-third?
Well, Matthew and Gina
will pay for half.
[Andrea] And Gabriel and I will...
No, I don't think
we need to go into detail.
[chuckles] Well, whatever.
- Anyway, SAM will be ours.
- [Chin] Love it.
[Gab] But for sure,
we'll need your help.
We need as many talents as we can get
to join SAM.
And maybe now is the best time
to start our Social Media division.
- Agree!
- For sure! I have so many ideas.
Of course, we won't be able
to handle all that
on top of everything else.
So Gab and I were thinking
of choosing one person
to head that division.
So Chin and I go head-to-head?
Camille too!
[Andrea] I know she's new,
but she's doing such a great job.
Who knows? She could make
a great Junior Manager.
- You all have an equal chance.
- Mm-hm.
- Yeah.
- So, good luck, guys!
[Daisy] Ladies and gentlemen!
How about some arroz caldo?
- [Gab] Arroz caldo?
- [Andrea] In this heat?
- I have packed lunch.
- Ms. Andrea.
- Yes?
- I'll head back to set
after I go home
for a change of clothes.
Sir Monsour lent his car and driver.
- Okay. How is Lav?
- Oh, Mr. Lav says
- he needs to speak to you urgently.
- Okay, please set it up.
- Let me know. Thank you.
- Okay.
- How about some steamed rice cake?
- I'll go get my lunch.
- [Gab] Let me have some of it.
- This'll do.
[Andrea] Come with me.
I don't want to have to return.
- [Gab] Put this on my tab, okay?
- [Daisy] Yes, Gab!
I've never been this nervous before.
I've auditioned many times before
but my heart was going so fast.
That's how it goes, get used to it.
What did they say?
I'm not sure, I couldn't read them.
Sir Gab, did they call yet?
You just got back! Relax.
Oh, by the way.
- Where's Joey? Thanks, bro!
- Hey, congrats!
[Sofie] I got him
a going-away present.
- Really?
- Mm-hm.
[Gab] He already went back to Lora's.
They have to start packing.
They're leaving soon.
- They're really going to Canada?
- [Gab] Yes.
[Sofie] No going-away party?
- A going-away party?
- [Sofie] Yeah.
For a six-year-old?
- Yeah!
- [Andrea] Why not? It'll be fun.
[Sofie] Right! Where do we have it?
Your place, Sir Gab?
No, his place is too small.
We'll do it here.
Hey, that's harsh.
But the AC's not working.
Then let's rent
some huge electric fans.
And Rina will take care of the food.
[gasps] Ma'am, I want in!
- [Andrea] Of course.
- Here's what we'll do.
I'll take care of everything.
Just tell Ms. Lora
to invite all of Joey's friends.
And let's invite Mother Aleta.
I want to see her in costume!
[Andrea] Oh, yeah, a costume party!
- Costume?
- This will be great!
- Everyone get your costumes ready.
- Costumes?
- For Joey's going-away party.
- Game? Game!
- [Sofie] Let's go!
- [all cheering]
- Game!
[dramatic music]
[wind chimes clink]
[Camille] That's what Mama said.
It was the Ad Congress.
He walked in...
You mean Pops.
Sir Matthew and Sir Paul walked in,
and they wanted haircuts.
They couldn't find a barber.
So they walked into Mama's salon.
That was it.
- From then on...
- From then on
he would go up to Baguio regularly.
Pops admitted that.
Mama doesn't remember.
Or maybe she just didn't notice.
Why did they break up?
[exhales sharply]
Maybe they got tired of it all.
I never asked Mama.
[Camille] But believe me,
we don't know you.
I mean, we know nothing about you.
All I know was that
Matthew had another family...
Yes, you are.
The other family that jerk had...
[shouts] Don't be mad at him!
[bed creaks]
[softly] Don't be mad.
It's not his fault.
I came to see him.
I wanted to work with him.
I wanted to be with him.
I'm not mad at him.
Besides, we always fight.
This is nothing new.
If you're not mad at him...
are you mad at me?
No.
Maybe a little, I don't know.
I don't like
seeing my mother this way.
She's always crying.
I don't know how to make her stop.
You're lucky.
You get to spend every day with him.
That's what you want, right?
What do you call him?
"Sir Matthew."
"Matthew."
Shoot.
So nobody knows? Not even one?
[Hector] You're going back
to the shoot?
Yeah, I hate my life.
- Why? [gasps]
- Ouch.
- Did you miss a step?
- Sorry.
Told you I'm exhausted. Sorry.
- Oh, god!
- What?
This is where I dropped you off
after our date.
Yeah, so?
- [gasps]
- Let's not talk about it.
- This is the last time.
- I know.
[Camille] You started it.
- Never again.
- Nothing happened.
- No. Nothing happened. Okay.
- Okay.
Yuck, bro.
You mean, "Big Bro".
Yes, Big Bro is right.
Right.
- Oh, the car's here.
- That's Monsour Del Rosario's car?
Yes, I borrowed it.
Gotta run, I'm going to be late.
- Call me!
- [Hector] Call me anytime.
[mouse clicks]
Sir Matthew?
What a big opportunity
this Junior Manager position is!
[Matthew mumbles]
- [Matthew] Oh...
- That's what I really want to do.
[Noemi] To manage talents
just like you do.
[in English] I mean...
You are my inspiration.
- I consider you my mentor.
- [high-pitched ringing]
[Matthew] Gina,
I came here to apologize.
It was a long time ago.
You would've never found out.
That is, if you didn't hire her
to work for you.
That bastard child of yours.
I didn't hire her.
She works for Andrea.
Do you know what you've done
to those children?
[Gina] I suppose you're here
for your check.
The money you're going to buy
your plaything with?
The money to pay for Shine?
[Gina] Why don't you just go ahead
and move to Galaxy?
That should solve all your problems.
[Noemi] Sir Matthew?
Sir Matthew?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Uh... What were you saying?
Is there anything you need me to do?
You know, so you can evaluate
my performance.
Nothing at the moment.
Oh, no, hang on, there is something.
Yes, Sir Matthew? Let me know.
- What is it, I'll take care of it.
- Here. Wait.
Can you get me three new shirts?
Just like this one.
But maybe other colors.
I'm sure you know my size.
Mm-hm.
- Hi.
- [Andrea] Oh!
[chuckles]
Ms. Gutierrez.
So good to see you again.
Why do you always give me
a hard time, Andrea?
- What?
- [Janine] Oh, please.
I know what you're doing, Andrea.
I was already in talks with HBO!
I want that part in Rob's film.
Why are you blocking this for me?
Janine, we've done no such thing.
As a team, we decided
that it is in our best interest
to have Rob supported
by an all-SAM cast.
And HBO agreed.
I'm surprised
your manager failed to inform you.
I haven't signed with Galaxy yet.
[Andrea] Well,
whether you sign or not
bottom line is,
if you're not a SAM artist
you can't be part of the project.
[frustrated sigh] So what do I do?
[in English] I want that part.
Then come back to SAM.
[scoffs]
[sighs]
I knew you were going to say that.
SAM is your home.
You belong with us.
This is a long-standing relationship.
And I agree with you.
You're perfect for this project.
But again,
you cannot be part of this project
if you are not a SAM artist.
And this thing you say I do?
I would do it for you.
I always do.
I don't want to audition.
I can have that arranged.
Just send me the contract.
I'm a good actor, Andrea.
I know.
But, Janine,
it's not always about talent.
[tense music]
WHAT'S THE TEA?
WITH OGIE DIAZ
Shh! Be quiet.
Be quiet.
They might find out
that we know all about their secret!
Who am I talking about?
The Power Couple
who's having marital issues.
That's tough!
From Sports Power Couple
to Power Outage.
[gasps]
The relationship is blacking out.
But what about their endorsements?
That's their livelihood.
I heard these two would often
go out in public
to show people that they're together.
That it's all good between them.
But behind the scenes, gosh...
The truth is, they have issues.
But please don't judge them.
You think they're putting on an act?
Oh, of course they'll do that.
It's just business.
Try to empathize with them.
But hold on. Here it is!
Let me give you a clue.
All you bashers out there...
POW!
...will get a taste of my fist!
Ouch!
[squeals]
WHAT'S THE TEA?
WITH OGIE DIAZ
- [Lav] Sound!
- [crew 1] Rolling!
[Lav] Camera!
- Action!
- [Monsour shouts, grunts]
[Lav] Exit!
Cut!
Lester.
- Show him. Demonstrate, just do it.
- Okay.
Monsour.
Monsour. Buddy.
We'll show you how we want it, okay?
- Just to nail the blocking.
- [Emir] Sir.
[Emir] JR, Lester, ready?
- [Lester] Ready.
- [Emir] Action.
[both grunt]
[Lav] Get up then exit right away.
Do it that way, okay?
Get the blowers ready! Come on.
Action!
[grunts]
[Lav] Action!
Exit now!
Cut! Emir!
What is it, sir?
He's doing it again!
Is there a rock there or something?
- I'll check.
- Is his foot stuck?
- [Emir] There's nothing here.
- [Lav] Okay, reset! Sound!
Wait, where's the alien guy?
- Camera!
- [crew 2] Take 17!
- [grunts]
- Cut!
[action music]
Wind, we need wind!
One more, one more!
- [Lav] Camera!
- [crew 2] Take 40!
Action!
Wait, is this the right spot?
How's my profile?
[Lav] Action!
[grunts]
Cut!
Hey, buddy?
How exactly do you run?
I don't do that.
I get in my car.
Okay, one more.
Let's finish this tomorrow, sir.
I need to be somewhere.
This is so easy.
I can do it with my eyes closed.
Tomorrow, I'll nail it in one take.
Camille.
[Camille] Sir?
Please tell Andrea I need to see her.
It's important that we talk soon.
- Yes, sir.
- This is urgent. ASAP.
- Okay.
- Tell her right away.
Uh, sir, don't you want to finish...
No, I don't.
I'll do it tomorrow.
That'll be easy.
- [Monsour] Bye.
- [Lav] Camille.
- Hey!
- [Emir] Camille.
Remember, you asked for this.
You wanted Lav to direct this movie.
What I really wanted was something
with an "international" vibe!
This is my comeback movie!
I thought you were ready
to go commercial?
I gave you everything you asked for
and I know...
no one watches action movies anymore.
But I agreed to do this project.
There's a certain quality
that my fans look for.
Those iconic
Monsour freaking Del Rosario moves!
Bam! Just like that!
You asked me
to write a normal script.
Where's the script?
Here is my Norte script.
[Lav] Forty pages.
This is Monsour's script.
A hundred and thirty pages.
The lines are so long!
Look at how fat that script is!
And I do nothing in it,
but cry and moan and think.
Where's the martial arts?
I agreed to keep it
under three hours.
That's a big ask but you got it!
We've shot several days.
I've done nothing but walk!
"Walk, Monsour, keep walking."
What kind of an actor is he?
What kind of director is he?
Can we replace him?
How? He's producing this!
[Monsour] This is my money
we're using.
I'm the lead actor.
But where's my face?
All you see are trees!
None of it is authentic.
"Monsour, you're overacting."
So what? A movie isn't real life.
Sir, there's one more thing.
What now?
I hate black and white!
Did he say why?
You can't see the blood!
An action movie in black and white!
You can't tell if it's blood or oil!
Darn, what the heck!
[chuckles] Goodness.
[in English]
It's all black and white!
The world is black and white!
[in Ilonggo]
You better stop him or else!
[in English] Color is an illusion!
[in Ilonggo] I hate working with him!
Find a way!
- [in English] Okay.
- Sorry.
[in Filipino] I'm calm now,
but I really need a drink.
Oh, Camille!
[in Ilonggo]
Get the fan here before I explode!
[in English] Old Fashioned? Bourbon?
- What do you want?
- Marijuana.
Marijuana?
[in Filipino]
We have that. Check in my office.
[in Ilonggo] Award-winning
international filmmaker, whatever!
[in English]
Please, Andrea, I'm begging you.
Can you fix this for me?
Of course!
[in Filipino] Don't worry, Lav.
I'll talk to the investors.
I'm sure we can figure something out.
[in English] Just give me time.
[in Filipino] Okay.
Make sure we can see the blood.
Convince them, Andrea.
Oh, of course!
Of course! The blood!
We'll know it's blood.
Oh, by the way.
We're having a party here.
- Please come.
- A costume party?
- I'll come if he won't.
- Monsour?
- Lav can't be here.
- Oh!
I'll make sure of that.
He won't be here.
- I'll make sure of that.
- [Lav] Okay, make sure.
- [Monsour] Okay, bye!
- Bye!
[Camille] Thank god for the fridge.
Whose fault is it?
They both have a point.
My god.
SAM can't lose this project.
Camille, we just can't!
[gasps] What's up?
Wanna join us, Ms. Daisy?
[Daisy] You want what I'm selling?
[Andrea] Sorry,
can't eat in this heat, Daisy.
[groans]
What heat?
[Daisy] What heat?
- [gasps]
- Does it come with batteries?
Of course!
- It's automatic!
- [Andrea] What is that?
- [Camille] Ms. Andrea...
- Ready to use!
And if you run out of batteries,
don't worry, because...
- These run on manual power!
- [Camille] Nice!
Go get my purse, now!
- No need. I have cash.
- You do?
- [Daisy] I can put it on your tab.
- Here.
But cash is good too!
What does this one do?
Madam.
This is what celebrities use on set.
Try it on.
- Ouch!
- I'm sorry.
- Can I use these at once?
- Like this.
[Sofie] This way, please.
[knocks on door]
Sir Matthew, he needs your signature.
[Matthew] Okay.
- [mailman] Thank you, sir.
- [Matthew] Thank you.
[tense music]
[Paul] Helen is livid!
She was ready to accept my offer
to buy Shine.
And now I'm withdrawing the offer.
[Matthew] Well...
Paul, what did you just send me?
[Paul] There's just one other offer
but I'm pretty sure Helen
isn't taking that offer.
That way, Andrea and Gabriel
can buy Shine.
And then you can move to us.
What you have in your hand
is your signing bonus.
And Matthew?
I'm so excited.
Okay, well, let me study it first.
I'll get back to you.
Yes, Camille?
Here, for the heat.
The others have theirs already.
- [Matthew] Thank you.
- Try it.
Make sure it works.
- [wind blows]
- Wow, it's strong!
- Let me get that.
- No, I'll do it.
- I'll do it.
- [Camille] It's okay, I have it.
Yes?
I just wanted to give you that.
Thank you.
Matthew.
I had a talk with Hector.
[in English]
Yes! I'm available on that day.
[Kelly] That's great, Gabriel!
That's the only time we could see you
otherwise we'd be waiting for a month
and we just can't wait that long.
[Gab] We're very excited to finalize
Kiray's contract for Women in Chains.
Great, we'll see you then.
Great! All right! See you!
[in Filipino] Sir Gab?
The meeting with Kelly Norman
is on Joey and Lora's departure.
- Oh, really?
- [Chin] Yes.
It should be a quick meeting.
I'll make it to the airport in time.
I hope you're sure about that.
- Here.
- [Gab] What's this?
- This heat is killing us.
- [Gab] Right.
[cell phone ringing]
[in English] Hello?
Yes, this is Gabriel Soler.
Sofie Lasola?
[in Filipino] Yes, absolutely!
[Gab] I'm looking at it right now.
Sorry, she's been on demand lately.
[in English] Okay, which role?
Okay, what page?
[Sofie] Okay.
- Thank you so much. Thank you.
- [Gab clears throat]
- [Chin] Sofie?
- Yes?
[in Filipino]
Sir Gab has something to tell you.
Uh...
You said you'll do it.
Uh, Sofie, about your audition.
Did I get it?
Yes, but
you're the secretary
who witnesses the argument.
Then you beg them not to kill you
but they kill you anyway.
So that's three lines.
But it's an acting piece!
It's a two-day shoot!
And an acting piece.
[Gab] It's a tiny part,
but it's a start.
Don't worry about this one.
Everyone starts with a small role.
[Chin] At least it's an acting piece!
[Gab] Just keep auditioning.
You'll get a big role eventually.
I'm going to be in a movie!
[shrieks]
- [Noemi] What's happening?
- I got the part!
[shrieks]
I got the part!
[cheerful music]
Careful!
- Aren't you tired?
- You're sweaty.
It's all crooked.
- [gasps]
- [Lora] Are you enjoying?
- [Joey] Yes, Mom.
- [kid] Come on, Joey!
- Hi.
- [Monsour] What's up?
- [Daisy] Sir Monsour!
- [Kiray] Uncle Gab!
- Is that Kiray?
- Kiray!
- [Lora] You're so pretty!
[squeals]
I didn't recognize you!
Everyone is having so much fun.
Oh, yeah! I'm having fun.
- And the food...
- You like it?
- It's okay?
- Of course!
You saved some for us, right?
Extra special for you, of course.
I love it!
[Matthew] Andrea?
[all cheering]
- Whoa!
- [guest] Can I take one more?
[Monsour] Of course.
Oh, who's that?
- [all cheering]
- [Andrea laughing]
[Andrea] Love it!
[crowd in unison] Sir Matthew!
- [pops]
- [kids cheering]
- [kid] Which superhero are you?
- [Andrea] Oh!
[Lav] Director. Indie Director.
[Andrea] Hi, Mr. Lav!
You made it!
Is it over? Can I go home now?
Come on, you just got here.
You can't leave.
We just wrapped the children's party.
It's the adults' turn this time.
Our receptionist Sofie here...
- Hi!
- ...auditioned for a movie
and she got the role!
We're celebrating her!
- Congratulations!
- [Sofie] Thank you so much, sir!
And someone wants to speak to you.
Oh, here we go. I knew it.
Come on, do it.
This talk will fix everything.
- Mon? Hi!
- Yeah?
- Hi!
- Surprise!
- Very surprising.
- All good, right?
Sure.
Indeed, it is.
- Mm-hm.
- Surprise.
Well...
What can I get you, sir?
The strongest drink you have.
You heard him.
Thank you.
- Sir.
- Uh... Mm-hm.
So...
I think it's time to finally talk
about your project...
Here? At a children's party?
Oh, we can go to the conference room
where it's more private, more adult,
and hopefully more civilized.
- Right? Let's go. Follow me!
- Okay.
Sure.
[Lora] Rina!
- The food was so good!
- It was!
- Thank you!
- Anything for these guys.
Thank you!
- Excuse me.
- Okay.
Uh...
I'm going to stay for a bit.
I'll just visit you guys later.
You don't have to. Look at this guy.
He's already tired.
Oh, there's no more playing tonight.
We'll see you at the airport, right?
- I will.
- Then stay here
and play with them.
Don't take us home. I'll handle it.
- Are you sure? Okay.
- Yes.
Thank you.
[indistinct chatter]
[Noemi] You've drunk way too much.
[loud crash]
[indistinct shouting]
[Gab] What was that?
- You're walking out on me?
- Stop this!
- You're angry at me?
- Please!
- Talk it out!
- Show me that anger!
I'm not angry!
When I'm angry, I make a movie!
- You're the one who's angry!
- Oh, my.
- [Andrea] Please stop!
- I don't understand your anger!
- [Lav jeers]
- Show it to me!
I'll show you!
- That's one!
- [all shout]
Two!
[indistinct shouting]
Mon! Stop! Please!
Three!
And my finishing move!
[shouts]
- Well, what the heck!
- Come on!
- Now I'm getting serious!
- Let's see what you got!
- Come on!
[Andrea] Mother!
- [Monsour] Mother!
- Hey!
- Good evening, Mother!
- Mother Aleta.
- Good evening.
- What's this about?
Good evening, Mother.
[Monsour] Good evening, Mother Aleta.
This is just a rehearsal, ma'am.
- We're just fooling around.
- [Lav] This is just practice.
- [Monsour] Just practicing.
- [Lav] Idiot.
You were supposed to talk it out
with your mouths, not your fists!
You boys drive me crazy!
This is your fault, man!
- You started it!
- You pulled my hair!
I did not pull your hair!
- I just tugged at it.
- [Andrea shouts]
My god!
Will you listen to yourselves?
It's like talking to schoolkids here!
Now will you please start over?
- Hey, buddy.
- Hm?
So that's the way you look at things?
I mean, your eyesight, your vision?
That's the only way you see things?
I'm not completely color blind.
I see blues and greens.
- Just like dogs.
- No red?
- No red.
- Well, we need that.
Let me tell you this.
The action movies you used to make?
Those with "ratatatat",
you against a hundred men?
[Lav] Pow, pow, pow!
That's all gone. It's different now.
[Monsour]
But that's what I'm used to.
How can I make
a comeback movie, when...
I can't do drama?
Yeah, right, you can't.
But you know
- I did read your script.
- [Lav] And?
- [Monsour] I loved it.
- [Lav] But?
But it doesn't go with my brand.
- It's too...
- Authentic.
- [finger snaps]
- That's it! It's too real.
You see, I make movies
so that people can escape reality.
And I make films to reveal the truth.
[Rina] How are your superpowers
holding up?
I have to look after these guys.
They might kill each other again.
Relax.
- Will you sit?
- But!
- Don't fly off in that cape!
- They drive me nuts!
You should have used your power!
[Andrea] It's one for all,
all for one!
- I was really feeling my outfit!
- [laughs]
It looks good on you!
Speaking of which,
do you have extra clothes for later?
If you go to work wearing that
you're going to get strange looks!
I remembered.
[giggles]
[in English] What if...
What?
What if I move in with you?
[playful music]
Wow.
[Noemi] My god!
Of all the places to fight in,
they choose the fountain!
[Camille] Hey, Noemi!
Hey, let me get that!
You can go back inside.
Don't you want to party with them?
Why are you always after what's mine?
Aren't you satisfied yet?
Are you okay? Is this a bad time?
What is it, Ms. Karylle?
I'm working on a little project.
Do you have time to help me?
What's it about?
It's the socials
for my Diva In Disguise persona.
Oh, I can try,
but I'm no good with stuff like that.
Besides, your mom
might not like this.
She won't be involved in this.
It's just the two of us.
And maybe Chin would like to join us.
Um...
I don't think he'll want to help me.
I don't think they like me very much.
It's fine, don't stress over it.
[chuckles]
[tuts]
[giggles] This will be
our own little thing, okay?
- [Karylle] Okay?
- Sure, I'll help you.
[giggles]
[approaching footsteps]
[sighs]
[exhales sharply]
So how are you?
[in English] Not too good.
What would Samuel do?
[in Filipino] You taught me that.
But not everything
that Samuel did was right.
Matthew.
Put in the work.
You do the thinking.
You figure out what you need to do.
Samuel is dead.
Stop bothering him.
Okay.
Time for me to go.
You just got here
and you're going home already?
And you?
Do you still go home?
[frustrated sigh]
Call my driver, I'm leaving.
Hey!
[Sofie] Hey, Sir Gab!
What are you doing here?
Trying to sober up.
I couldn't keep up with the others!
Thank you.
For what?
For Joey. He was so happy!
Did you see him?
That huge smile never left his face.
I think it only disappeared
when he fell asleep.
Come on, Sir Gab.
I'd do anything for Joey.
And for you too.
Sir Gab.
Thank you so much
for believing in me.
Thank you very much.
I mean, look at me.
I'm going to be in a movie!
I still can't believe it.
Well, you deserve it.
Hey! Monsour and Lav are at it again!
[Gab] Hey, what's going on?
[staff] It's Mr. Lav and Sir Monsour!
- [Sofie] Huh?
- [Gab] Mr. Lav.
- Bang! Bang!
- [Lav laughs]
A quick step backward and bam!
Oh, gosh.
Then I turn to them and go...
[imitates gun fires]
I'll go after the master and go
"Bam! Take that!"
Huge explosion, man!
That's how we made movies back then!
[Lav] I saw that, man!
And your movie Fierce!
It's so wild, man!
Heck, no!
- So freaking wild!
- Wild?
What about you?
You made a head
with another face at the back!
And that thing
you had Charo Santos do?
Looking for her son on the floor
while the camera spun around her?
Man, if that isn't crazy! Wild!
Not everyone
who's at the top is successful.
And not everyone at the bottom
is a loser.
We each have a place in this world.
Wherever you are right now,
you're there
because you are the only one
who can do what you do.
That should be your attitude.
[rock music]
[man snores]
[snoring continues]
We've been infiltrated.
- Did you see it?
- What happened?
- You saw it?
- How did Ogie know?
I have no idea.
Where's Matthew?
I've been texting him.
How did the press find out...
Deo?
The AC's still not working!
What happened? Have you fixed it?
Someone broke in.
- Someone broke in?
- Into the AC?
[Chin] Oh, it's so cheap.
- [Camille shushes]
- Hey.
[shushes]
[whispers] There's someone in there!
[Sofie] What? Someone broke in?
Who is it?
What do we do?
- Let's make our move.
- Go ahead.
Someone call security.
Wait!
No, wait. You have the key, right?
So use it!
[indistinct chatter]
[Chin] Hey!
[Gab] Be careful!
[Daisy] How did he get inside?
[Camille] It's Sir Matthew's office!
[Daisy] Who could that be?
- [gasps]
- [Gab] Sorry!
[Daisy] You pushed her!
- [Gab] Hey!
- [Camille] Deo, no!
You're a janitor, not a murderer!
- [thuds]
- [Matthew yells]
What?
[grunts]
[Andrea] Matthew?
- [Gab] Matty?
- [Noemi] Sir Matt?
- [Chin] Did they say it was Matthew?
- [Gab] How...
Two weeks?
Something like that.
Wait.
So you knew Camille was his daughter?
My god, of course not!
If I knew, then you would too.
Maybe you kept it from me.
Why didn't you tell us?
[hesitates] Maybe I was embarrassed.
- What's happening?
- I don't know.
- Wait.
- It's so hot.
You're ashamed that she's your kid?
No!
I'm ashamed to admit it to you guys.
- Matthew.
- Well...
I didn't want to impose.
I didn't wanna ask you to hide this
and lie to everyone else.
Come on, Matty.
You didn't have to hide.
And why stay here at the office?
You could've stayed at a hotel.
Don't tell me money is an issue.
Aah!
What?
Oh, my god.
You don't have to do that.
I'll tell you everything.
That surprised me.
We already know.
Noemi, go ahead.
There's something between
you and Sir Matthew.
[whimpers]
Matthew's my father.
Hec is your brother?
Did you come to Manila
to ask Matthew to help you get work?
No.
I don't know, maybe.
[Camille] All I know is...
I want to be with him.
I want to get to know him again.
Wow, Noemi.
Looks like this fight is unfair.
We have to be really extra now.
[Sofie] The bosses aren't like that.
How do you know?
[scoffs]
Yeah, we're not sure
who to trust here.
I should go.
I need to give out calling cards.
I'm interested in becoming
a Junior Manager, Chin.
Really?
Why should we believe
anything you say?
Come on, Noemi.
[Daisy] What are you guys doing here?
Let's go back to reception.
Don't worry about them.
They're just being mean
because they're so stressed out.
- Come on!
- You go ahead.
I'll be there in a bit.
[Sofie] Okay,
don't make me wait too long.
What are we going to do, Matt?
We already told everyone
we're buying SAM.
And this thing with Brandon,
how did this get out?
The advertisers will kill us!
It's been out since last night.
I even saw it.
But it was too late to do anything.
[in English] But don't worry,
I'll take care of that.
And SAM?
I'll handle that too.
You just have to...
You just have to trust me.
Okay, but, Matt...
You can't stay here anymore.
[in Filipino]
Don't do this to yourself!
I'd let you stay with me,
but Rina's moving in.
Oh, wow, congrats!
- I know, right?
- Oh, wow indeed.
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Fine.
You can stay with me.
[in English]
Just until we figure everything out.
- You sure?
- I'm sure.
[in Filipino] Go shower.
We have a lot of work to do.
Thank you.
[thrilling music]
[inaudible dialogue]
Why is it so hot here?
- Gross, you haven't paid your bill?
- Oh, sorry.
- Megan? Hi!
- Hi!
I missed you!
- How are you?
- I'm okay!
- I missed you! Say hi to my vlog!
- Hi!
Hi, Sir Gab.
- [Yuki] Hello!
- Hey, Yuki!
- Hi!
- [Gab] Hi!
- How are you...
- It's hot.
Sorry, the AC is being fixed.
- Here, use this.
- [Yuki] Thank you.
How may I help you?
[sighs] Okay, here goes.
So I wanted to stay in this hotel
with my friends
we want to celebrate his birthday.
Because you know, 22 is huge, right?
I mean, 22 years on this Earth!
- I'm so proud of him!
- Wow. Yay.
But the hotel backed out!
[Yuki] Like, they backed out.
- I'm super mad.
- [Gab] Wow, okay.
So sorry to hear that.
Did you get a refund?
How much did you pay them?
- No, I wrote to them.
- You wrote them a check?
No, I emailed them.
- Huh?
- No, it's like this.
[Yuki] I emailed them,
you know, the stuff.
I told them I wanna stay there
with my friends
and celebrate my friend's birthday.
You know, the works.
I told them
that I have 8.4 million followers...
Wait, let me check.
Yup, it's 8.4 million followers.
And we're going to promote them
on all my social media platforms.
And you know how it goes...
the shebang, shebang, the richness.
All that. But...
They backed out!
Man, it's hot.
Uh, Yuki, "back out" means
you had a prior arrangement
but one of the parties "backed out".
[Gab] Here, it doesn't sound like
you had an arrangement at all.
No, but it's rude!
Like, it's so rude.
I mean, do they not know
what I can do for their business?
- [Yuki] Am I right?
- [Gab] Okay.
- [Yuki] They should appreciate me.
- [Gab] What...
What do you want us to do?
Well, you're my manager.
You know what to do.
So make them say yes.
[scoffs]
That's not how it works.
How does it work?
Chin? Noemi? Camille?
[Yuki] How?
Can you guys tell me?
[Chin] So, Yuki,
here's what we can do...
[chuckles]
Be careful what you wish for.
So now it's just me.
It sure is.
Just send Camille over
when you're done.
- [Gab] No, I'll do it.
- Go back in there.
- [Gab] What do you need?
- No.
I'll do it for you.
How are Sir Monsour and Mr. Lav?
They're still talking.
- [Andrea] Camille, can I trust you?
- Ma'am?
[in English]
Knowing that Matthew is your dad
and you work for me
can I trust you?
[in Filipino]
Of course you can, Ms. Andrea.
You can trust me.
[in English] Thank you.
[Karylle exclaims]
[Camille] Now...
everyone is doubting me.
[Karylle] Even Andrea?
[exhales sharply]
Especially Ms. Andrea.
It's an initial reaction.
I mean...
they were surprised.
They were bombarded with all
this info about you and Matthew.
But it'll sort itself out.
Soon.
No family is perfect.
Everything is gonna be okay.
[thrilling music]
WHAT'S THE TEA?
WITH OGIE DIAZ
All right, the latest from the mill.
I'm getting the jitters
because we've been talking
about breakups
celeb couple problems, politics.
But this one is different.
Check this out.
A popular actor...
Wait, is he still popular?
[laughs]
And a director. They made a scene.
That's right.
[Ogie] The two were invited
to the baptism
of a talent manager's child.
And what happened?
It was rooted
in the disagreements they had
from the action film they're doing.
It's crazy.
So, at the baptism,
things got heated really quickly.
It was an all out fistfight!
Kung Fu here, Karate there.
Goodness!
Both of them were soaked
with holy water!
Did that cleanse them of their sins?
[laughs] Of course not.
Mr. Director and Mr. Actor
start confessing your sins!
What you're doing isn't right.
You're driving me nuts.
WHAT'S THE TEA?
WITH OGIE DIAZ
Sorry about the mess.
It's okay.
Andrea is...
lending us her extra mattress.
Are you okay on the couch for now?
Yeah. Don't worry about me.
Actually...
this is softer than the one
at the office.
[Gab] Here you go.
Thank you!
Uh...
Matty.
It'll work out.
We'll find a way.
Yeah, thanks.
Oh, by the way.
Do you snore?
No, not me.
Good, I'm a light sleeper.
I can't room with someone who snores.
I wake up easily.
- No problem.
- Okay.
[Gab] Good night!
Yeah, good night!
[light music]
[Gab snores]
[snores]
[snores loudly]
[Lav] Bam!
Pow, pow! You make a turn!
You hit! Kick!
Elbow! Bam!
Bam!
Explosion, take cover, run!
Run!
You take a tumble.
There's more by the door.
Bam, bam! You take their gun.
Tak! Tak! Tak!
Ratatatatat!
Simple.
That's it.
Very simple.
Lav, I have a question.
Don't worry about the blood!
It'll be all bloody!
Real and CGI!
I want to know
my character's motivation.
What drives my character.
Your what?
What I want to know is
where my character is coming from.
I mean, must he beat up everyone?
[Lav] It's an action movie.
Why not talk to them calmly?
That sounds like a good idea.
[clicks tongue]
Camille.
- [Camille] Yes, sir?
- What's up with him?
He's going method on me.
This is an action movie.
I don't...
- [Lav] Talk to him.
- I don't...
I want the old him back.
How much longer, Deo?
The heat is unbearable!
I know what I must do.
But I'm only human.
And when the bough breaks
the cradle will fall.
You broke the bough, SAM!
[Sofie] What?
There is an end to everything.
Let me go get the vacuum cleaner.
It's so hot!
We're a devil short of hell here!
- Gab!
- Yeah?
Where's Matt?
He still won't get up.
He's got a lot of work to do.
Let's give him space.
He'll get up soon.
To vanquish us all?
[chuckles] He might.
[laughs]
I'm going.
Home?
I told you.
Rina's moving in today.
It will be a few trips back and forth
so I have to be home.
Well, you seem excited!
- [Gab] Okay. Take care!
- [Andrea] Bye! See you!
- Chin?
- Yes?
I need these photocopied, please.
- Four copies for our meeting later.
- Sure.
- I'll make it ten just to be sure.
- Okay, good.
START
[machine whirring]
- Will you be long?
- [Camille gasps]
[Camille] No. I'm done.
Almost done, sorry.
Just a few more.
Your turn.
- [Sofie] Thank you!
- Sof, I need your stapler.
[Sofie] Sure, here you go.
By the way,
Sir Gabriel also needs a copy.
- Sorry, I forgot.
- [Camille] Oh, okay.
It's fine.
I'll leave this here.
[Camille] Chin, are you done?
I need one more copy for...
You left this.
That might be important for your dad.
Please don't tell anyone.
He hasn't signed anything yet.
And he doesn't know I have a copy.
[Chin] Oh, please.
I don't care about any of that.
But I'm staying in SAM.
Should I tell Ms. Andrea?
You know what?
Stay out of it.
They'll just fight over this.
What happens to SAM?
I mean, can she and Sir Gab
handle SAM
without my dad...
without Sir Matthew?
That's not your problem.
Just stay out of it.
Thank you, Chin.
Okay, sure.
[somber music]
[in English]
"Love me when I least deserve it."
[in Filipino] That's about right.
In your darkest moments
you'll need the power of true love.
I've asked this of so many women.
Only one agreed.
[Rina] Careful, babe.
[chuckles]
What is all this stuff, honey?
You said "move in",
so I'm moving in with everything.
- I think that's it for this batch.
- Okay.
How many more trips?
A couple more.
Okay.
- Go on now!
- Okay.
- I'll see you later!
- [Andrea] Yup!
Don't work too hard.
Hurry up, but be careful, okay?
- [Rina] Okay, bye, see you!
- Bye!
Okay.
[grunts]
You stand out, so you go first.
[clatters]
[gasps]
Okay.
[chuckles]
[exhales sharply]
[breathes heavily]
[frustrated yell]
[closing theme music]